ZULLY BARRIENTOS

Product professional with 6+ years of experience across product management and UI/UX design. I excel at collaborating with diverse stakeholders and bringing order to the often chaotic product development process. Core skills: production, business process development, research, prototyping and writing.

TOOLS

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

Azure DevOps

InDesign

Illustrator

Photoshop

Adobe XD Sketch

Figma

InVision

MyBalsamiq

GitHub Visio

Usability Hub

MICROSOFT | Redmond, WA

Producer, Oct. 2019 - Present

• Gaming producer for the Performance and Environment Content Tech Artist teams at 343 Industries, supporting the upcoming AAA title Halo: Infinite

Xbox Live Program Manager, Apr. 2019 - Sep. 2019

- Conducted user research and market analysis to identify feature/functional requirements for a new Xbox parental controls mobile app
- Created information architecture design and wireframing for entire app

BEAUTY BAKERIE | San Diego, CA

Digital Product Designer, Oct. 2018 - Feb. 2019

• Helped increase online conversion by creating playful yet polished email and web campaigns as well as experimental landing pages to highlight UGC

LANGUAGES

CSS3 HTML5

JavaScript

English Spanish

Portuguese

AGUILAR CASTILLO LOVE | San José, Costa Rica

Web Designer & Brand Consultant, Dec. 2017 – Oct. 2018

- Led brand identity and content development for print and web
- Executed the design of a custom responsive website using WordPress

M POWERED STRATEGIES, INC. | Washington, D.C. IT Project Manager & Graphic Designer, Oct. 2014 – Oct. 2017

- Lead for the firm's rebranding project; included overhaul of company's visual identity, corporate messaging and a new responsive website
- \bullet Redesigned waterfall SDLC processes into agile methodology for all IT projects across the Department of Veterans Affairs' (VA) IT office (OI&T)

SKILLS

Production

Product Management

UI/UX Design User Research Info. Architecture

Wireframing Prototyping

Writing
Illustration

EDUCATION

BLOC | Bootcamp

UI/UX Design and Front End Development apprentice, 2019

UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA, SAN DIEGO | La Jolla, CA

Master of Public Policy and Management, 2014

AMHERST COLLEGE | Amherst, MA

Bachelor of Art & Art History, 2011